Mariana Pircalabescu

53/1 Crewe Road West, Edinburgh
Mobile: 07587635575; Email: yo_sweet_mary@yahoo.com

Profile

Confident and with significant relevant experience in customer service, sales representative, production operative, I'm a hardworking person, able to work effectively as a part of a team or under own initiative. I'm very organised and able to adapt to new environments quickly.

Key Skills

Experience in providing face-to-face customer service in the hospitality industry- good customer service skills.

Organising the equipment for factory's workers, successfully completed- good organisation skills.

Achievement- achieved great sales results by introducing personal care products based on glycerine in the pharmacies for the first time in the company.

Work Experience

| Production | Operative/ | packing. | Burton's | Biscuits |
|-------------------|------------|-----------|-----------------|----------|
| | O polativo | pavitiigi | Daitonio | Diocuito |

May 2017 - Apr 2020

Ability to work quickly and accurately to meet production targets. Good observation skills, Reliable.

Waiter, Emy Bar (Italy)

Apr 2006 - Apr 2017

Good experience in providing face-to-face customer service

Waiter, Sunrise Beach Bar (Romania)

Mar 2000 - Aug 2004

Delivering beverages and food in a timely manner. Check in with guests to ensure if they are ok with everything.

Sales Representative, Civiti Srl

Feb 1998 - Jan 2000

Presenting, promoting and selling products to existing and prospective customers. Establishing, developing and maintaining positive business and customers relationships.

Education

| National Progression Award in Data Science Level 4 | 2022 |
|--|------|
| The Safer Food Group Level 2 award in food safety for Manufacturing, CPD certified | 2017 |
| Local Centre of Tourism (Romania) Qualification certificate (hotel receptionist)-6 month | 2000 |
| ATP -Constanta (Romania) Qualification certificate (secretary) -3-month | 1997 |
| Industrial High School (Romania) -theoretical Pathway High School Diploma | 1996 |

Additional Information

Hobbies and interests

Additional Information:

- -Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point)-good
- Italian language (good speaking)

Hobbies: Travelling, Reading, Dancing, Gardening, Yoga.